nymcu.org 2018-12-31

# FACTS

 FACTS
FACTS            WHAT DOES MUNICIPAL CREDIT UNION DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL
                 INFORMATION?
                 Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
 Why?            consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you
                 how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice
                 carefully to understand what we do.
                 The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you
 What?           have with us. This information can include:
                      Social Security number and income
                      Account balances and payment history
                      Credit history and credit scores
                 When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in
                 this notice.
                 All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday
 How?            business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their
                 customers’ personal information; the reasons Municipal Credit Union chooses to share; and
                 whether you can limit this sharing.
                                                            Does Municipal Credit          Can you limit this
Reasons we can share your personal information
                                                                 Union share?                   sharing?
For our everyday business purposes -
such as to process your transactions, maintain your                   Yes                          No
account(s), respond to court orders and legal
investigations, or report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes –
to offer our products and services to you                             Yes                          No
For joint marketing with other financial companies                    Yes                          No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes -
                                                                       No                    We Don’t Share
information about your transactions and experiences
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes -
                                                                       No                    We Don’t Share
information about your creditworthiness
For nonaffiliates to market to you                                     No                    We Don’t Share
Questions? Call Within N.Y. City & Long Island (212) 693-4900; outside N.Y. City & Long Island
                 (800) 323-6713

Page 2
Who we are
 Who is providing this notice?    MUNICIPAL CREDIT UNION
What we do
 How does Municipal Credit Union  To protect your personal information from unauthorized access
 protect my personal information? and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.
                                  These measures include computer safeguards and secured files
                                  and buildings.
 How does Municipal Credit Union  We collect your personal information, for example, when you
 collect my personal information?
                                          Apply for a loan or open an account
                                          Deposit money or withdraw money
                                          Use your credit card or debit card
                                  We also collect your personal information from others, such as
                                  credit bureaus and other companies.
 Why can’t I limit all sharing?   Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                          Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes –
                                           information about your creditworthiness
                                          Affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                          Sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                  State laws and individual companies may give you additional
                                  rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
 Affiliates                       Companies related by common ownership or control. They can
                                  be financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                          Municipal Credit Union has no affiliates
 Nonaffiliates                    Companies not related by common ownership or control. They
                                  can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                          Municipal Credit Union does not share with nonaffiliates
                                           so they can market to you.
 Joint marketing                  A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies
                                  that together market financial products or services to you.
                                          Our joint marketing partners are insurance companies
                                           and financial products or services companies.
                                                                                    Rev.06/18
